Southbound straight past Norwood.
Train doors hiss, head lowered.
Croydon board on a rainy day. Mum said
learn, but I learn the estate way. Wingstop,
Morley's, chips in the rain.
Zigzag path from the class to the train.
Concrete maze and
the clock born haunted.
Blue light flash, that's constant,
not random.
Man's got dreams of a house with a drive,
but man got beef and a
Back in the day,
South Norwood was divided between three
crews.
You had the Holmesdale Boys, the HF
Fanatics,
the Selhurst Mandem,
and the Al-Masid Brothers.
Then Croydon got worse,
and predators came knocking.
Penge, West
Norwood.
Then Big Joe came along,
convinced everyone that there's strength
in numbers.
Took three crews, made them
one, and recruited a protege.
Me, Liam
Blake.
Then Big Joe went
down.
Your generals want to know who's in charge.
Have you decided? Yeah.
None of them.
Me? Take over?
Yeah, his lawyer was sure. Why?
I'm just his advisor.
My thoughts exactly, bruv.
Easy, bruv.
Big Joe knows what he's doing.
I ain't saying he doesn't.
But Liam, no disrespect, bruv,
you're not a leader.
Sash, you're with me, right?
And we-- I don't know,
man. We've got to talk about this,
all four of us.
A crown I didn't want.
Generals thinking about rebellion.
I hope Big Joe is right about me.
Or this all ends.
JD bag and a tear in my Coke.
Still hit ends like I'm proud
of the post code.
See ya. This is Croydon.
Blaze in the cold wind. Yeah.
South side living.
Bare pain that I hold in. High road
love, but my heart stay frozen.
Still on my outside.
Word is Holmesdale's looking at a proper
rebellion.
Good. I'll tell the others